Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2 5583/2
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Box: 30, folder: (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Contract of Wages and Working Conditions Between Kennecott Copper Corporation Utah Copper Division And Company's Employees, Publication (Box 30, Folder 10)
    January 27. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Contract Of Wages and Working Conditions Between Kennecott Copper Corporation Utah Copper Division And Company's Employees, Publication (Box 30, Folder 10)
- Box: 30, folder: (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Application For Employment Kennecott, Publication (Box 30, Folder 11)
- Box: 30, folder: (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Summary Of Medical Benefits Plan Supplementary To Medicare, Publication (Box 30, Folder 12)
    August 24. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Your Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: Summary Of Medical Benefits Plan Supplementary To Medicare, Publication (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: Life Insurance Non-Occupational Accidental Death Or Dismemberment Insurance Weekly Indemnity For Accident And Sickness, Publication (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Item 5: Summary of Life Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Item 6: Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Item 7: Program Of Scholarships And Fellowships, Publication (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Item 8: Summary Of Medical Benefits Plan, Publication (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Item 9: Summary Of Medical Benefits Plan, Publication (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Item 10: Summary Of Life Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Item 11: Hospital, Medical And Surgical Benefits, Publication (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Item 12: Kennecott Medical Plan For Salaried Employees On The New York Office Plan, Publication (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Item 13: Helping to secure your future", Publication (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Item 14: Reetirement Plan for Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Item 15: Your Personal Statement Of Benefits, Publication (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Item 16: Your Savings And Investment Plan, Publication (Box 30, Folder 12)
- Box: 30, folder: (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: A Suggestion could easily Hit Pay Dirt, Publication (Box 30, Folder 13)
- Box: 30, folder: (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Supervisors' Newsletter, Publication (Box 30, Folder 14)
- Box: 30, folder: (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Fair Housing, Publication (Box 30, Folder 15)
- Box: 30, folder: (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Desegregated Apartments: Experience in Louisville, Publication (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: Information Concerning Complaints, Publication (Box 30, Folder 16)
- Box: 30, folder: (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Negro Employment In Kentucky State Agencies, Publication (Box 30, Folder 17)
- Box: 30, folder: (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Rules and Regulations of the Unemployment Insurance Commission, Publication (Box 30, Folder 18)
- Box: 30, folder: (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Commonwealth Of Kentucky Personnel Rules, Publication (Box 30, Folder 19)
- Box: 30, folder: (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: University Hospital Employee Information, Publication (Box 30, Folder 20)
- Box: 30, folder: (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Kermac News, Publication (Box 30, Folder 21)
- Box: 30, folder: (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Every Monday Morning, Publication (Box 30, Folder 22)
- Box: 30, folder: (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Employees Handbook, Publication (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Item 2: Wage and Fringe Information, Publication (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Item 3: Employees Handbook, Publication (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Item 4: Quality and You, Publication (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Item 5: Story Of The Kittinger Company, Inc, Publication (Box 30, Folder 23)
- Box: 30, folder: (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: On The Square Inc., Publication (Box 30, Folder 24)
- Box: 30, folder: (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: An Exposition Of The Methods Of The United Hatter of North America As Applied To The Knox Hat Works, Publication (Box 30, Folder 25)
    By Robert J. Mac Farland. Item is in English.
- Box: 30, folder: (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Kohler Of Kohler News, Publication (Box 30, Folder 26)
- Box: 30, folder: (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Getting Acquainted at Kohler Co., Publication (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Item 2: Getting Acquainted at Kohler Co., Publication (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Item 3: Getting Acquainted at Kohler Co., Publication (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Item 4: Getting Acquainted at Kohler Co., Publication (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Item 5: Getting Acquainted at Kohler Co., Publication (Box 30, Folder 27)
- Box: 30, folder: (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Kohler Co., Publication (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Item 2: Law and Order Breaks Down in Kohler and Sheboygan, Wisconsin, Publication (Box 30, Folder 28)
    August 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Lafollette Committee References To Kohler Co. (1939), Publication (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Item 4: Kohler Co., Publication (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Item 5: Highlights And Chronology Of The UAW-CIO Strike At Kohler Co., Publication (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Item 6: Herbert V. Kohler's Statement to the Senate Rackets Committee, Publication (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Item 7: Kohler Of Kohler Reuther Has Lost a 14-Month-Old Strike, Publication (Box 30, Folder 28)
    By Chesly Manly. May 28. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: For Release Upon Delivery Of Lyman C. Conger Argument, Publication (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Item 9: For Release Upon Delivery Of Lyman C. Conger Argument, Publication (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Item 10: Law and Order Breaks Down in Kohler and Sheboygan, Wisconsin, Publication (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Item 11: For Release Upon Delivery Of Lyman C. Conger Argument, Publication (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Item 12: The American Tragedy, Publication (Box 30, Folder 28)
    By Herbert V. Kohler. November 17. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: To Risk a Violent Strike Or Die of Attrition, Publication (Box 30, Folder 28)
    By Herbert V. Kohler. May 27. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Can A Free Economy Tolerate Union Violence? The Meance of UAW-CIO Coercion, Publication (Box 30, Folder 28)
    By Herbert V. Kohler. February 25. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: To Risk a Violent Strike --Or Die of Attrition, Publication (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Item 16: In Freedom's Cause The Menace of UAW-CIO Coercion, Publication (Box 30, Folder 28)
    By Herbert V. Kohler. April 17. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Are Unions Above The Law?, Publication (Box 30, Folder 28)
    By Herbert V. Kohler. December 9. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: The Right To Work, Publication (Box 30, Folder 28)
    By Herbert V. Kohler. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Kohler Of Kohler April News 1955, Publication (Box 30, Folder 28)
    April 5. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Kohler of Kohler, Publication (Box 30, Folder 28)
    July 27. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: For Immediate Release, Publication (Box 30, Folder 28)
    July 5. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: NLRB Finds Kohler Co. Guilty, Publication (Box 30, Folder 28)
    August 26. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Kohler Co., Publication (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Item 24: Kohler In Non-Compliance With NLRB Order, Claim, Publication (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Item 25: For Immediate Release, Publication (Box 30, Folder 28)
    August 6. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: For Immediate Release, Publication (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Item 27: Memorandum, Publication (Box 30, Folder 28)
    Ocotber 18. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Reuther vs. The Workingman's Freedom, Publication (Box 30, Folder 28)
    By Barry Goldwater. May 18. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Irresonsible Power, Publication (Box 30, Folder 28)
    By Raymond Moley. April 28. Item is in English.
- Box: 30, folder: (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: A Deliberate "Plug" For the Kohler Co., Publication (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - Item 2: The Right To Work, Publication (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - Item 3: Kohler of Kohler, Publication (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - Item 4: In Freedom's Cause The Menace of Uaw-CIO Coercion, Publication (Box 30, Folder 29)
- Box: 30, folder: (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: People, Publication (Box 30, Folder 30)
- Box: 30, folder: (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Kopper News, Publication (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - Item 2: The Nemo Plant, Publication (Box 30, Folder 31)
- Box: 30, folder: (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Employee Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - Item 2: Kroehler Emmployees Investment Program, Publication (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - Item 3: Your Kroehler Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - Item 4: Your Group Insurance Plan UIU Health And Welfare Fund, Publication (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - Item 5: Kroehler employees pension plan, Publication (Box 30, Folder 32)
- Box: 30, folder: (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: working together at Kroehler, Publication (Box 30, Folder 33)
- Box: 30, folder: (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Annual Report/1964, Publication (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - Item 2: 1964 Annual Report, Publication (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - Item 3: Progressive Grocer, Publication (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - Item 4: The Kroger Co. Annual Report, Publication (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - Item 5: The Kroger Co. Annual Report 1961, Publication (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - Item 6: 1951 Pay Check, Publication (Box 30, Folder 34)
- Box: 30, folder: (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Educational Subsidy For Regular Employees, Publication (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - Item 2: A Report On Your Prudential Group Life Insurance, Publication (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - Item 3: Scholarship Program, Publication (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - Item 4: Kroger Employees' Profit Sharing And Retirement Income Program, Publication (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - Item 5: Kroger Employees' Profit Sharing and Retirement Income Program, Publication (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - Item 6: Management Benefit Program, Publication (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - Item 7: Profit Sharing and Retirement Income Program, Publication (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - Item 8: Amendment No. 2 To Form S-1 Registration Statement, Publication (Box 30, Folder 35)
    January 31. Item is in English.
- Box: 30, folder: (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Operation Future, Publication (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - Item 2: Application For A Management Position With The Kroger Co., Publication (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - Item 3: Application For A Management Position With The Kroger Co., Publication (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - Item 4: Employment Application, Publication (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - Item 5: Educational Subsidy For Regular Employees, Publication (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - Item 6: How Well Does Main Street Know You?, Publication (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - Item 7: Our Vote is our Voice!, Publication (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - Item 8: A Pain in the Lane, Publication (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - Item 9: Behind the Front!.., Publication (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - Item 10: Every Mrs. Smith Wears a Halo!, Publication (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - Item 11: You and the Kroger team, Publication (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - Item 12: You and the Kroger team Office Personnel, Publication (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - Item 13: You and Kroger, Publication (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - Item 14: Personal History, Publication (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - Item 15: Personal History, Publication (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - Item 16: You and the Kroger team, Publication (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - Item 17: You and the Kroger team Office Personnel, Publication (Box 30, Folder 36)
- Box: 30, folder: (Box 30, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Today's Progress Equal Opportunity, Publication (Box 30, Folder 37)
  - Item 2: Today's Progress Equal Opportunity, Publication (Box 30, Folder 37)
  - Item 3: Joint Statement On "Plans For Progress", Publication (Box 30, Folder 37)
  - Item 4: Joint Statement On "Plans For Progress", Publication (Box 30, Folder 37)
- Box: 30, folder: (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Consumer Dynamics in the super market, Publication (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - Item 2: Personnel Department, Publication (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - Item 3: Personnel Department, Publication (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - Item 4: Organizational Chart Corporate Office, Publication (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - Item 5: Organizational Chart Corporate Office, Publication (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - Item 6: Organizational Chart Corporate Office, Publication (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - Item 7: Organizational Chart Corporate Office, Publication (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - Item 8: Fine Foods in the Making, Publication (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - Item 9: Housewife, You're My Boss, Publication (Box 30, Folder 38)
    By Joseph B. Hall. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Business Week, Publication (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - Item 11: 3-D marketing: Democracy, development & decentralization triple Kroger sales, Publication (Box 30, Folder 38)
    November 7. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: History Of The Kroger Co., Publication (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - Item 13: The Kroger Co., Publication (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - Item 14: Barney Kroger had an Idea!, Publication (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - Item 15: A Penny Plus Was Made By US In 1952, Publication (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - Item 16: "Pretty Wonderful Isn't It?", Publication (Box 30, Folder 38)
- Box: 30, folder: (Box 30, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: The LEC Newsletter, Publication (Box 30, Folder 39)
- Box: 30, folder: (Box 30, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: The Toledo Plan For Industrial Harmony, Publication (Box 30, Folder 40)
- Box: 30, folder: (Box 30, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: The Toledo Plan For Industrial Harmony, Publication (Box 30, Folder 41)
- Box: 30, folder: (Box 30, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Maritime Program Imperatives A Time For "Deeds-Not Words", Publication (Box 30, Folder 42)
    May 12. Item is in English.
- Box: 30, folder: (Box 30, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: What It Takes, Publication (Box 30, Folder 43)
- Box: 30, folder: (Box 30, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: Laclede News, Publication (Box 30, Folder 44)
- Box: 30, folder: (Box 30, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Freedom's Frontiers Unlimited, Publication (Box 30, Folder 45)
    By Nathan W. Shefferman. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: You Can't Collect On Collectivism, Publication (Box 30, Folder 45)
  - Item 3: To The Union Label Trades Department of the American Federation of Labor Convention, Publication (Box 30, Folder 45)
    September 14. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Industrial Relations Human Relations The Historical Road To Free Enterprise, Publication (Box 30, Folder 45)
  - Item 5: Let's not be Easy Marx, Publication (Box 30, Folder 45)
  - Item 6: Labor's Stake in Capitalism, Publication (Box 30, Folder 45)
- Box: 31, folder: 1 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Confidential, Publication (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Three Men and An Idea, Publication (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Supervisors' Handbook, Publication (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Box: 31, folder: (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: For Immediate Release, Publication (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: The Plight Of The Living Theatre, Publication (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: For immediate release, Publication (Box 31, Folder 2)
    May 17. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: A Statement By Louis A. Lotito President Of The League Of New York Theatres, Publication (Box 31, Folder 2)
    By Louis A. Lotito. May 17. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Producers' View: Request by Union Would Raise the Price of Tickets, Publication (Box 31, Folder 2)
    By Robert L. Joseph and Alexander H. Cohen. May 8. Item is in English.
- Box: 31, folder: (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Threats to the Battle Against Disease, Publication (Box 31, Folder 3)
    By James Daniel. October. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Employee's Handbook, Publication (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: The Scatter Gun, Publication (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Personnel Procedures, Publication (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Box: 31, folder: (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Under The Federal Government's New Withholding System, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Introducing, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Are You Aware, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: No Flu Shots This Year, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: With This Friday's Paychecks, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Personnel Relations News, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: A Letter Was Mailed Yesterday, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
    November 19. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: We Have Always Been Impressed By, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Box: 31, folder: (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: In Congressional Debate on Right-to-Work Laws, Publication (Box 31, Folder 5)
    April 19. Item is in English.
- Box: 31, folder: (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: A Brief Outline of The History of Cement, Publication (Box 31, Folder 6)
    By Joseph S. Young. Item is in English.
- Box: 31, folder: (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Schedule of Pay Rules And Regulations fo rthe Government of Conductors, Baggagemen, Trainmen, Yardmen and Switchtenders, Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Box: 31, folder: (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Government Control of Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Job Classification Its Effects Upon Promotion And Security, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Organizational Tactics, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: A Close-Up On Production, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Box: 31, folder: (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Protection For You AndFor Your Family, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Building For The Future Your Share of Lever Profits Income for Your Retirement Years, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Your Lever Security Package, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Box: 31, folder: (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Employment With Lever Brothers Company, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Box: 31, folder: (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Working Agreement Association of Employees of Lever Brothers Company's, Publication (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Union-Management Co-Operation At The Toronto Factory Of Lever Brothers Limited, Publication (Box 31, Folder 11)
    By W. R. Dymond. February. Item is in English.
- Box: 31, folder: (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Welcome To Lever, Publication (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Welcome to Lever House, Publication (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: Lever in 1960, Publication (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: Lever Brothers Company, Publication (Box 31, Folder 12)
    February 24. Item is in English.
- Box: 31, folder: (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Lever Standard, Publication (Box 31, Folder 13)
- Box: 31, folder: (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Libby's Scanner, Publication (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Personal Wallet Card, Publication (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: The Scanner, Publication (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: Diamonds Are a Girl's Best Friend!, Publication (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Item 5: dateline, Publication (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Item 6: dateline, Publication (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Item 7: dateline, Publication (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Item 8: dateline, Publication (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Item 9: dateline, Publication (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Item 10: Libby's Scanner, Publication (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Item 11: dateline, Publication (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Item 12: Suggestion, Publication (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Item 13: Libby's Annual Report for th eyear ended July 3, 1965, Publication (Box 31, Folder 14)
    July 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Libby's Scanner, Publication (Box 31, Folder 14)
    September, October, November. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Worldwide Map, Publication (Box 31, Folder 14)
- Box: 31, folder: (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: General Information Regarding The Company, Publication (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: This Is Libby's, Publication (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: 85 Years of Progress, Publication (Box 31, Folder 15)
- Box: 31, folder: (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Libby's Scanner, Publication (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: Genera Instructions, Publication (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: dateline, Publication (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Item 4: dateline, Publication (Box 31, Folder 16)
- Box: 31, folder: (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Important Information For Employes, Publication (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: a plan of Major Medical Benefits, Publication (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: look where the action is, Publication (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Item 4: Three Men and An Idea, Publication (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Item 5: Application For Employment, Publication (Box 31, Folder 17)
- Box: 31, folder: (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Summary of Employee Benefits, Publication (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: Salaried Employees' Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: A Plan Of Major Medical Benefits, Publication (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: Your New Improved Group Life and Disability Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Item 5: Pension Trust Plan, Publication (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Item 6: Salaried Employees' Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Item 7: hospitalsurgical and medical plan, Publication (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Item 8: Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Item 9: Hospital Medical and Surgical Plan, Publication (Box 31, Folder 18)
- Box: 31, folder: (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Salaried Employe's Statement For Group Life And H&A Insurance, Publication (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: Certificate Of Age, Publication (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Item 3: Program of Hourly Employe Benefits, Publication (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Item 4: Your Group Health Expense Plan, Publication (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Item 5: Salaried Employes Supplemental Retirement Plan of Libby-Owens-Ford Company, Publication (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Item 6: L-O-F Educational Assistance Plan For Employees, Publication (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Item 7: Program of Insurance, Salary Continuance, And Retirement Benefits For Salaried Employes, Publication (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Item 8: Libby-Owens-Ford Application For Enrollment Or Change, Publication (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Item 9: Basis For Determination Of Withholding, Publication (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Item 10: Application For Major Medical Expense Insurance, Publication (Box 31, Folder 19)
- Box: 31, folder: (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: WE of Libbey Owens Ford, Publication (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Item 2: Employment Opportunities, Publication (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Item 3: Other Policies, Publication (Box 31, Folder 20)
    June 24. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Standard Vacation Policy for Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Item 5: Employee Background Questionnaire, Publication (Box 31, Folder 20)
- Box: 31, folder: (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: The LOF Glass News, Publication (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Item 2: The LOF Glass News, Publication (Box 31, Folder 21)
    August-September. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The LOF Glass News, Publication (Box 31, Folder 21)
    April-May. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Annual Report, Publication (Box 31, Folder 21)
- Box: 31, folder: (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Our Group Benefit Plans, Publication (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Item 2: Outline of Savings and Retirement Plan for Liberty Mutual People, Publication (Box 31, Folder 22)
- Box: 31, folder: (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: among oursleves, Publication (Box 31, Folder 23)
- Box: 31, folder: (Box 31, Folder 24)